directions__001	directions__002	directions__003	directions__004	directions__005	directions__006	directions__007	directions__008	directions__009	directions__010	direction	title	ingredients
"1. Combine breadcrumbs, onion, olive oil, salt, pepper, and ground turkey in a medium bowl. Mix with hands until well-blended. Form mixture into four patties, about 1/2-inch thick."	"2. Heat a grill pan or griddle over medium-high heat. Place patties on grill pan. Cook 3 to 5 minutes per side, until completely cooked through. The juices should run clear when poked with a knife. Once patties are flipped, top each with a slice of cheese. Transfer burgers to warmed buns. Serve immediately with choice of toppings."									"=CONCATENATE(A2,"" "",B2)"	Kid-Friendly Turkey Burgers 	1 1/2 cups fresh breadcrumbs
												"1/2 onion, very finely chopped"
												1 tablespoon olive oil
												1/2 teaspoon salt
												1/4 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper
												1 1 /2 pounds ground turkey meat
												4 slices cheddar cheese
												"4 buns, warmed"
												"Lettuce, sliced tomato, sliced red onion, pickle for serving"
												"Ketchup, mustard, mayonnaise, for serving"
Combine all of the ingredients in a cocktail shaker. Shake well. Strain into a cocktail glass.											Tropical Rainstorm 	1 1/2 ounces dark rum
												1/2 ounce cherry brandy
												1/2 ounce lemon juice
												1 teaspoon Cointreau or Triple Sec
												3 or 4 ice cubes
												
												
												
												
												
												
"Whisk 1/2 cup beer, malt vinegar, mustard seeds, and dry mustard to blend in small bowl. Let mixture stand at room temperature 3 hours."	"Transfer beer-and-mustard-seed mixture to blender; add remaining 1/2 cup beer, horseradish, 1 teaspoon coarse salt, 1 teaspoon pepper, honey, and ground caraway seeds; blend until coarse puree forms. Transfer mixture to medium metal bowl. Set bowl over saucepan of simmering water and whisk often until mixture thickens slightly, about 15 minutes (mixture will be thinner and more sauce-like than store-bought mustard). Transfer mustard to small saucepan and add cornstarch mixed with 1 tablespoon water; whisk over medium-high heat until mustard thickens and boils, about 2 minutes. Transfer mustard to airtight container. Cover and chill until cold. DO AHEAD: Can be made 1 week ahead. Keep chilled."	"Sold at specialty foods stores, Indian and Asian markets, and online at thespicehouse.com. If unavailable, use yellow mustard seeds instead."									Beer and Horseradish Mustard 	"1 cup lager beer, divided"
												2/3 cup malt vinegar or red wine vinegar
												1/3 cup whole brown mustard seeds* (about 2.2 ounces)
												2 tablespoons dry mustard (such as Colman's)
												1/4 cup prepared white horseradish
												1 teaspoon coarse kosher salt
												1 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper
												1 tablespoon honey
												"1/4 teaspoon caraway seeds, finely ground in mortar with pestle or in spice mill"
												2 teaspoons cornstarch mixed with 1 tablespoon water
"Preheat oven to 400°F. Lightly grease 15 1/2x10 1/2x1-inch jelly roll pan. Stir 1/2 cup butter, coffee, 1/2 cup cocoa and vegetable oil in heavy small saucepan over medium heat until smooth. Remove saucepan from heat. Stir flour, sugar, baking soda and salt in large bowl until blended. Whisk in cocoa mixture. Whisk buttermilk, eggs and 1 teaspoon vanilla in medium bowl until blended. Add to flour mixture and blended well. Spread batter in prepared pan."	"Bake cake until tester inserted into center comes out clean, about 20 minutes. Transfer cake to rack."	"Meanwhile, stir milk and remaining 1/2 cup butter and 1/4 cup cocoa in heavy medium saucepan over medium heat until smooth. Bring mixture to boil, stirring constantly. Remove from heat.Add powdered sugar and remaining 1 teaspoon vanilla and whisk until smooth."	Spread frosting over warm cake. Sprinkle with pecans. Cool cake completely and serve.								Mocha Sheet Cake with Pecans 	1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter
												"1 cup strong brewed coffee or 1 tablespoon instant coffee, dissolved in 1 cup hot water"
												3/4 cup unsweetened cocoa powder
												1/2 cup vegetable oil
												2 cups all purpose flour
												2 cups sugar
												1 teaspoon baking soda
												1/2 teaspoon salt
												1/2 cup buttermilk
												2 large eggs
												2 teaspoons vanilla extract
												6 tablespoons milk
												1 1-pound box powdered sugar
												"1 cup chopped pecans, toasted"
"Toast bread; butter lightly. Heat heavy large nonstick skillet over medium-high heat. Cook pancetta over medium heat until crisp. Transfer to paper towels to drain. Crack eggs into drippings in same skillet, keeping yolks whole. Cook until edges are opaque and whites are nearly set, about 3 minutes. Carefully turn eggs over. Cook until whites are set, about 1 minute. Put each egg on slice of toast. Add arugula to same skillet. Cook until just beginning to wilt, about 30 seconds. Top eggs with cheese, then pancetta and arugula. Top with remaining slices of toast and serve."											Fried Egg Sandwiches with Pancetta and Arugula 	4 1/2-inch-thick slices 4x4-inch egg bread or sourdough bread
												Butter
												2 ounces thinly sliced pancetta
												2 large eggs
												2 ounces arugula (2 cups lightly packed)
												"1 ounce Parmesan cheese, shaved"
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
"Melt butter in heavy large deep skillet over high heat. Add squash; sauté 1 minute. Add broth, syrup, thyme, salt, and 1/4 teaspoon pepper; bring to boil. Cover, reduce heat to medium, and cook until squash is almost tender, 8 to 10 minutes. Using slotted spoon, transfer squash to large bowl. Boil liquid in skillet until thickened, 3 to 4 minutes. Return squash to skillet. Cook until tender, turning occasionally, 3 to 4 minutes. Season with more pepper, if desired."											Maple-Braised Butternut Squash with Fresh Thyme 	6 tablespoons (3/4 stick) butter
												"1 3- to 31/2-pound butternut squash, cut lengthwise in half, peeled, seeded, cut into 1-inch cubes"
												1 1/4 cups low-salt chicken broth
												1/3 cup pure maple syrup
												1 tablespoon minced fresh thyme
												1 teaspoon coarse kosher salt
												1/4 teaspoon (or more) black pepper
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
"Preheat oven to 400°F. Unfold pastry onto work service. Using 2-inch- diameter scalloped cookie cutter, cut out 12 rounds. Using 1-inch-diameter cookie cutter, cut out centers of 6 pastry rounds. Discard centers. Pierce 2-inch rounds all over with fork. Brush edges with egg glaze. Top with pastry rings, pressing gently. Transfer to large baking sheet. Bake until puffed and golden, about 10 minutes. Transfer to rack; cool. Pull out uncooked portion from centers of pastries and discard. (Can be made 8 hours ahead. Store airtight at room temperature.)"	"Preheat oven to 325°F. Cook bacon in heavy medium skillet over medium-high heat until crisp. Using slotted spoon, transfer bacon to paper towels. Pour 3 tablespoons bacon drippings into small bowl. Discard all but 1 teaspoon of remaining drippings from skillet. Add shallots to drippings in skillet; sauté over medium-high heat until tender, about 3 minutes. Add Port and cranberries and bring to boil, scraping any browned bits. Boil until cranberries are soft and liquid is reduced by half, about 10 minutes. Add reserved 3 tablespoons bacon drippings and stir just until warm. Pour vinegar into small bowl. Gradually whisk in Port mixture."	"Meanwhile, place pastries on baking sheet. Spoon 1 heaping tablespoon cheese into center of each. Bake until cheese is soft, about 6 minutes."	Place endive in large bowl. Pour warm dressing over and toss. Divide greens among 6 plates. Sprinkle with bacon. Top each with 1 pastry and serve.								Curly Endive Salad with Cranberry-Bacon Vinaigrette and Blue Cheese Pastries 	"1 sheet frozen puff pastry (half of 17 1/4-ounce package), thawed"
												"1 egg, beaten to blend (glaze)"
												"9 smoked bacon slices, chopped"
												1/3 cup minced shallots
												1 cup ruby Port
												1/2 cup dried cranberries
												1 tablespoon balsamic vinegar
												6 heaping tablespoons crumbled blue cheese
												9 cups bite-size curly endive
												
												
												
												
"Preheat oven to 350°F. Lightly butter and flour 9 standard (1/3-cup) muffin cups. Sift flour and next 5 ingredients twice into medium bowl. Mix 6 tablespoons lukewarm water with vanilla in small bowl. Using electric mixer, beat brown sugar and butter in large bowl until light and fluffy. Add flour mixture in 3 additions alternately with water mixture in 2 additions, beating batter until blended after each addition."	"Using electric mixer fitted with clean dry beaters, beat egg whites in medium bowl until soft peaks form. Gradually add 2 tablespoons sugar and beat until firm glossy peaks form. Fold 1/3 of whites into batter to lighten, then fold in remaining whites. Spoon 1/4 cup batter into each prepared muffin cup."	"Bake muffins until tester inserted into center comes out clean, about 17 minutes. Cool muffins in pan on rack at least 20 minutes. Remove muffins from pan and cool completely on rack. DO AHEAD: Can be made 1 day ahead. Return muffins to muffin pan; cover and store at room temperature."	"Melt butter in large nonstick skillet over medium heat. Sprinkle sugar over butter in skillet, then place apple slices and pear slices in single layer (if possible) atop sugar. Increase heat to medium-high and cook without stirring until fruit is golden on bottom, pressing out to single layer as fruit cooks and reduces in volume, about 8 minutes. Turn fruit over in skillet and cook until golden, about 5 minutes. Add cranberries and cook until juices in skillet are reduced by about half, about 2 minutes."	"Heat half and half in heavy large saucepan over medium heat just until heated through and bubbles form at edge of pan. Whisk sugar, egg yolks, and sea salt in medium bowl; whisk in cornstarch."	"Gradually add hot half and half to yolk mixture and whisk until blended. Return custard to same saucepan; stir over medium heat until custard boils and thickens, 2 to 3 minutes. Whisk in butter, then 2 tablespoons brandy. Remove from heat."	"Brush top of muffins several times with remaining 4 tablespoons brandy until absorbed. Place 1 muffin in each of 8 bowls, cups, or dessert glasses. Divide caramelized fruit among bowls. Spoon warm custard over muffins and fruit in bowls (about 1/3 cup for each). Chill at least 30 minutes. DO AHEAD: Can be made 2 hours ahead. Cover and keep chilled. Let stand at room temperature 20 minutes before serving."					Caramelized Winter Fruit Custards 	1 cup cake flour
												3/4 teaspoon baking powder
												1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon
												1/4 teaspoon ground nutmeg
												1/8 teaspoon ground cloves
												1/8 teaspoon fine sea salt
												6 tablespoons lukewarm water
												1 teaspoon vanilla extract
												1/2 cup (packed) golden brown sugar
												"1/4 cup (1/2 stick) unsalted butter, room temperature"
												"2 large egg whites, room temperature"
												2 tablespoons sugar
												6 tablespoons (3/4 stick) unsalted butter
												3/4 cup sugar
												"2 large Granny Smith apples (about 1 pound), peeled, quartered, cored, cut into 1/3-inch-thick slices"
												"2 small Bosc pears (12 to 14 ounces total), peeled, quartered, cored, cut into 1/3-inch-thick slices"
												1 cup fresh or frozen cranberries
												2 cups half and half
												1/2 cup sugar
												4 large egg yolks
												1/4 teaspoon fine sea salt
												1 tablespoon cornstarch
												1 tablespoon unsalted butter
												"6 tablespoons apple brandy (such as applejack or Calvados) or poire Williams (clear pear brandy), divided"
"Put the rum, lemon peel, cinnamon and cloves in a pewter tankard or any heavy 12-ounce mug that has been rinsed in very hot water to warm it. Heat the cider or water to the boiling point and pour into the spiced rum. Add the pat of butter and stir well. Grate a little nutmeg on top. A cube of sugar may be added as well."											Hot Buttered Rum 	2 or 3 ounces dark rum
												Twist lemon peel
												Stick cinnamon
												2 cloves
												Sweet cider or water
												1 tablespoon sweet butter
												Nutmeg
												
												
												
"In a small bowl stir together chili powder, brown sugar, cayenne, and salt. On a work surface sprinkled with 2 tablespoons parsley roll out 1 sheet puff pastry into a 12-inch square. Sprinkle square evenly with half of spice mixture and 3/4 cup Cheddar, pressing cheese gently onto pastry. Roll up 1 edge to middle of pastry sheet and roll up parallel edge in same manner so that the 2 rolls are touching. Repeat procedure with remaining parsley, pastry sheet, spice mixture, and Cheddar. Wrap pastry rolls in plastic wrap and chill 30 minutes. Pastry rolls may be made 2 weeks ahead and frozen, wrapped well in refrigerator 2 hours before proceeding."	Preheat oven to 375°F.	"Cut pastry rolls with a sharp knife crosswise into slices just under 1/2 inch thick and arrange 1 inch apart on large baking sheets. Bake palmiers in batches in middle of oven 20 minutes, or until golden brown, and transfer with a metal spatula to racks to cool."									Spicy Cheddar Palmiers 	1 1/2 tablespoons chili powder
												1 1/2 tablespoons Firmly packed light brown sugar
												3/4 teaspoon cayenne
												3/4 teaspoon salt
												"1/2 cup packed fresh parsley leaves, washed, spun dry, and chopped"
												"a 17 1/4-ounce package frozen puff pastry sheets (2 pastry sheets), thawed"
												1 1/2 cups shredded sharp Cheddar (about 6 ounces)
"Preheat oven to 425°. Toss orange and lemon slices with 1 tablespoon oil on a rimmed baking sheet; season with salt and pepper. Roast citrus, tossing occasionally, until lightly charred in spots and starting to caramelize, 10-15 minutes. This makes the citrus flavor more complex. Let cool."	"Meanwhile, combine onion and lemon juice in a large bowl; season with salt and pepper and let sit 5 minutes (onion will soften a bit and get slightly sweeter and less harsh)."	Add roasted citrus to bowl with onion along with arugula and mint. Drizzle remaining 3 tablespoons oil over; season with salt and pepper and toss everything to combine and coat.	Add avocado and very gently toss until lightly dressed (you don't want to crush the avocado).								Roasted Citrus and Avocado Salad 	"1 blood or Valencia orange, sliced 1/8"" thick, seeds removed"
												"1 Meyer or regular lemon, sliced 1/8"" thick, seeds removed"
												"4 tablespoons olive oil, divided"
												"Kosher salt, freshly ground pepper"
												"1/4 small red onion, thinly sliced"
												2 tablespoons fresh Meyer or regular lemon juice
												"1 bunch watercress or arugula, thick stems trimmed"
												1/2 cup fresh mint leaves
												"1 avocado, cut into wedges"
												
												
												
												
												
"Sprinkle gelatin over water in a small heavy saucepan and let stand 1 minute to soften. Stir in cream and 1/8 tsp salt, then heat gently over medium-low heat, stirring, until gelatin has dissolved."	"Whisk together yogurt, honey, and almond extract, then whisk in cream mixture."	"Pour mixture into 4 small bowls and chill, covered, until set, at least 8 hours."	"Mince lemon thyme with sugar, then toss with peaches. Let macerate, stirring occasionally, at room temperature 20 minutes. While peaches macerate, let panna cotta stand at room temperature."	Top bowls of panna cotta with peaches and their juice. Drizzle with additional honey if desired.							Panna Cotta with Lemon-Thyme Peaches 	1 1/4 teaspoon unflavored gelatin (from a 1/4-ounce envelope)
												2 tablespoon water
												1 1/4 cups heavy cream
												1 cup plain low-fat yogurt
												1/4 cup mild honey
												1/8 teaspoon pure almond extract
												1 1/2 tablespoon fresh lemon-thyme leaves
												1 tablespoon sugar
												"3 peaches, peeled if desired, pitted, and thinly sliced"
												
												
												
												
Finely grind cumin seeds in an electric coffee/spice grinder or with a mortar and pestle.	"Thinly slice bottom 6 inches of lemongrass, discarding remainder. Purée lemongrass, shallots, garlic, ginger, cumin, sugar, salt, turmeric, cayenne, and water in a food processor, scraping down side occasionally, until as smooth as possible, about 2 minutes. (Paste will not be completely smooth.)"	"Heat 3 tablespoons oil in a 10-inch heavy skillet over moderate heat until hot but not smoking. Add lemongrass paste, then reduce heat to moderately low and cook, stirring constantly, until paste begins to stick to bottom of skillet and is very thick, 8 to 12 minutes. Transfer paste to a bowl and cool to room temperature, about 10 minutes."	"Pat lamb chops dry and rub lemongrass paste all over them, then arrange in 1 layer in a 13- by 9-inch dish. Marinate, covered and chilled, at least 12 and up to 24 hours."	Prepare grill for cooking over direct heat with medium-hot charcoal.	"Grill lamb on a lightly oiled grill rack, covered only if using a gas grill, loosening lamb from grill with a metal spatula, turning over occasionally, and moving around on grill when flare-ups occur, 9 to 11 minutes total for medium-rare. (Some of lemongrass paste will fall off.) Transfer chops to a platter and let stand, loosely covered with foil, 10 minutes. Discard wooden picks."	"Whisk together lime zest and juice, remaining 1/4 cup oil, and salt and pepper to taste. Spoon over chops and sprinkle with herbs."					Grilled Lemongrass Lamb Chops with Herbs 	"1 1/2 teaspoons cumin seeds, toasted and cooled"
												"3 fresh lemongrass stalks, root ends trimmed and 1 or 2 tough outer leaves discarded from each"
												"2 large shallots, chopped (1/2 cup)"
												"4 garlic cloves, chopped"
												1 1/2 tablespoons chopped peeled fresh ginger
												1 1/2 tablespoons sugar
												1 teaspoon salt
												1/2 teaspoon turmeric
												1/4 teaspoon cayenne
												3 tablespoons water
												1/4 cup plus 3 tablespoons vegetable oil
												"6 (1 1/4-inch-thick) loin lamb chops (2 to 2 1/2 lb total), end flaps secured with wooden picks"
												1/4 teaspoon finely grated fresh lime zest
												1 tablespoon fresh lime juice
												1/2 cup small fresh basil leaves
												1/4 cup small fresh mint leaves
												1/4 cup fresh cilantro leaves
"In medium bowl, whisk together crème frîache, honey, cumin, coriander, salt, and pepper. Sauce can be made up to four hours in advance, covered, and refrigerated until ready to use."	Preheat oven to 300°F.	"Pat ribs dry and sprinkle with salt and pepper. In heavy large sauté pan over moderately high heat, heat olive oil until hot but not smoking. Working in batches, sear ribs until golden brown, 4 1/2 to 5 minutes per side. Transfer ribs as done to platter; do not wash pan."	"In same pan, combine onions, carrots, celery, garlic, and rosemary. Sauté, stirring often, until soft, about 15 minutes. Add red wine and bring to boil. Lower heat to moderate and continue simmering until reduced by about 10 percent, about 3 minutes. Add stock and bring to simmer. Return ribs to pan, cover, and braise in oven until desired doneness (125°F for medium-rare, about 1 hour). Transfer ribs to cutting board and let stand 15 minutes. Lower oven to 125°F."	"Have ready large bowl ice water. In medium saucepan over high heat, bring salted water to boil. Add peas and boil, uncovered, until tender, 2 to 3 minutes. Drain in colander, then immediately plunge colander into ice water to stop cooking. Drain again. Coarsely chop, transfer to medium bowl, add onion, and toss to combine."	"In small bowl, whisk together olive oil, lemon juice, salt, and pepper. Drizzle over pea-onion mixture and toss to combine."	"In heavy large sauté pan, heat vegetable oil until hot but not smoking. Cut racks into individual ribs."	"In medium bowl, whisk together flour, semolina, and Parmigiano-Reggiano."	"Working in batches of 6, dredge ribs in flour mixture and fry until golden and crisp, 2 to 2 1/2 minutes per side. Transfer as done to paper towel-lined plate. Keep warm in oven while frying remaining batches."	"Ladle sauce into middle of large platter. Pile ribs on top, then top with salad. Sprinkle with cumin, coriander, and salt and serve immediately."		Crispy Lamb Spare Ribs with Honey Crème Fraîche and Chopped Pea Salad 	1 cup crème frîache
												1/2 cup honey
												"1 tablespoon whole cumin seeds, toasted and finely ground using spice or coffee grinder (about 1 teaspoon ground)"
												"1 tablespoon whole coriander seeds, toasted and finely ground using spice or coffee grinder (about 1 teaspoon ground)"
												1/2 teaspoon kosher salt
												1/4 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper
												6 pounds Denver lamb ribs (lamb breast spareribs; 6 small racks)
												3 teaspoons kosher salt
												3 teaspoons freshly ground black pepper
												2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil
												"4 onions, coarsely chopped"
												"8 carrots, coarsely chopped"
												"8 stalks celery, coarsely chopped"
												"2 heads garlic, cloves peeled and coarsely chopped (about 1/2 cup total)"
												"4 tablespoons fresh rosemary, coarsely chopped (from 12 sprigs)"
												4 cups dry red wine
												1 quart veal or chicken stock or low-sodium chicken broth
												"2 cups frozen peas (from one 10-ounce package), unthawed"
												"1 red onion, finely chopped"
												1/4 cup extra-virgin olive oil
												2 tablespoons fresh lemon juice
												1/2 teaspoon kosher salt
												1/4 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper
												2 cups vegetable oil
												1 cup all-purpose flour
												1 cup semolina flour (pasta flour)
												"1/2 cup Parmigiano-Reggiano, finely grated"
												"1 tablespoon whole cumin seeds, toasted and finely ground using spice or coffee grinder (about 1 teaspoon ground)"
												"1 tablespoon whole coriander seeds, toasted and finely ground using spice or coffee grinder (about 1 teaspoon ground)"
												1/2 teaspoon kosher salt
"Bring 3 1/4 cups broth to boil in heavy large saucepan over medium-high heat. Mix in orzo and simmer uncovered until just tender but still firm to bite and some broth still remains, stirring occasionally, about 8 minutes. Remove from heat. Add green onions and cheese and stir to blend. Season pilaf to taste with salt and pepper. Rewarm over low heat, if necessary, and mix in more broth by 1/4 cupfuls if pilaf is dry. Transfer pilaf to large bowl and serve."											Orzo Pilaf with Green Onions and Parmesan Cheese 	3 1/4 cups (or more) canned low-salt chicken broth
												1 pound orzo (rice-shaped pasta)
												"5 green onions, thinly sliced"
												3/4 cup grated Parmesan cheese
												
												
												
												
												
"Bring cranberries, horseradish, sugar, and water to a simmer in a 3-quart heavy saucepan over moderate heat, stirring with a wooden spoon until sugar is dissolved. Simmer, uncovered, stirring and mashing berries frequently with spoon, until berries break down, 5 to 10 minutes."	Serve sauce warm or at room temperature.										Cranberry Horseradish Sauce 	1 (12-oz) bag fresh or frozen cranberries
												"1 (6-oz) jar prepared horseradish, including juice, or 1/4 cup firmly packed finely grated peeled fresh horseradish"
												2/3 cup sugar
												1/3 cup water
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
"Combine pork, coriander, half of garlic, and 1 tablespoon salt in a large bowl; season with pepper and toss. Cover; chill at least 4 hours."	"Preheat oven to 350°F. Toast pumpkin seeds on a rimmed baking sheet, tossing occasionally, until golden, about 5 minutes; set aside."	"Toast chiles on clean baking sheet until slightly darkened, about 5 minutes. Let cool slightly, then remove stems, and seeds, if you prefer less heat. Place chiles, half of yellow onion, remaining garlic, and 1 cup hot water in a blender; let sit 10 minutes to soften chiles. Blend until smooth; set chile purée aside."	"Heat oil in a large Dutch oven over medium-high heat. Working in batches, cook pork, turning occasionally, until browned, 8–10 minutes; transfer to a plate."	"Pour off fat from pot. Cook chile purée in pot over medium-high heat, stirring occasionally, until reduced by half, 8–10 minutes. Add pork, oregano, remaining yellow onion, and 10 cups water to pot; season with salt and pepper. Bring to a boil, reduce heat, and simmer, partially covered, skimming occasionally, until pork is very tender, 3–3 1/2 hours."	"Add squash to stew and cook, uncovered, until pork is falling apart and squash is soft, 30–35 minutes; season with salt and pepper."	"Toss red onion and lime juice in a small bowl; let sit, tossing occasionally, 30 minutes."	"Serve stew with red onion, cilantro, and reserved pumpkin seeds."	"DO AHEAD: Pork can be marinated 2 days ahead; keep chilled. Stew can be made 3 days ahead; let cool, then cover and chill."			Pork and Squash Stew with Chiles 	"3 pound boneless pork shoulder (Boston butt), cut into 2"" pieces"
												1 tablespoon ground coriander
												"10 garlic cloves, finely chopped, divided"
												"1 tablespoon kosher salt, plus more"
												Freshly ground black pepper
												1/2 cup raw shelled pumpkin seeds
												6 dried New Mexico or guajillo chiles
												2 chiles de árbol or 1/2 teaspoon crushed red pepper flakes
												"2 large yellow onions, cut into 1/8""-thick wedges, divided"
												2 tablespoons vegetable oil
												4 sprigs oregano
												"1/2 kabocha squash (about 1 pound), peeled, seeds removed, cut into 1"" pieces"
												"1 delicata squash, seeds removed, cut into 1/2""-thick slices"
												"1/2 small red onion, thinly sliced"
												1/4 cup fresh lime juice
												Cilantro sprigs (for serving)
Coat a nonstick pan with cooking spray; sauté chicken over medium-high heat until cooked through. Remove from pan. Add oil and sauté garlic and ginger until garlic is golden. Add vegetables; cook until tender. Return chicken to pan; stir-fry 3 minutes.	"For the sauce, whisk 1 1/2 tbsp hot (not boiling) tap water into peanut butter to blend. Add soy sauce, vinegar, and hot sauce and mix. Divide stir-fry and sauce onto 2 plates. Serve each over 3/4 cup brown rice."										Chicken Stir-Fry with Peanut Sauce Over Rice 	Vegetable-oil cooking spray
												"6 oz boneless, skinless chicken breast, sliced"
												1 tsp sesame oil
												"2 cloves garlic, minced"
												1 tsp minced fresh ginger
												"3 1/2 cups of your favorite vegetables, chopped"
												1 1/2 tbsp peanut butter
												1 tsp low-sodium soy sauce
												1 tbsp rice vinegar
												Hot chile sauce (to taste)
"If using bonito flakes, in a bowl stir together flakes, vinegar, and soy sauce and let stand 1 hour."	"Peel and seed cucumbers and diagonally cut into 1/8- to 1/4-inch-thick slices. In a colander set over a bowl toss cucumbers with salt and drain 30 minutes. Rinse cucumbers well and pat dry. Pour bonito mixture through a fine sieve into a large bowl and toss liquid with cucumbers and 1 tablespoon sugar; if not using bonito flakes, toss cucumbers with vinegar, soy sauce, and 1 tablespoon sugar, or to taste. With scissors cut nori lengthwise into thin strips."	Serve salad garnished with nori strips.									Japanese Cucumber Salad with Vinegar 	3 heaping tablespoons bonito flakes* (optional)
												1/4 cup Sherry vinegar or rice vinegar
												1 tablespoon dark soy sauce
												2 English cucumbers or 4 regular cucumbers
												1 tablespoon coarse salt
												"1 tablespoon sugar, or to taste"
												Garnish: a 1- by 2-inch piece toasted nori* (dried laver) from one 8- by 7 1/2-inch sheet (optional)
												*available at Japanese markets and some specialty foods shops.
												
												
												
												
"Place potatoes in small saucepan. Add enough water to cover by 1 inch. Sprinkle with salt. Bring to boil and cook until potatoes are tender, about 10 minutes. Drain. Cool. Cut potatoes into thin slices."	"Preheat oven to 450°F. Sprinkle rimless baking sheet with cornmeal. Roll and stretch pizza dough to 16x11-inch oval. Transfer to baking sheet. Mix 1 tablespoon olive oil and garlic in small bowl. Brush garlic oil over dough. Sprinkle 3/4 of green onions over, then mozzarella, leaving 1/2-inch plain border. Top with potato slices and goat cheese. Toss asparagus and 1 tablespoon oil in medium bowl. Scatter asparagus over pizza. Sprinkle with Parmesan, then lightly with salt and generously with pepper."	"Bake pizza until crust is browned and asparagus is tender, about 18 minutes. Transfer to cutting board. Sprinkle with remaining green onions. Cut into pieces."									"Asparagus, Fingerling Potato, and Goat Cheese Pizza "	5 ounces fingerling potatoes
												Cornmeal (for sprinkling)
												Pizza Dough
												"2 tablespoons extra-virgin olive oil, divided"
												"1 garlic clove, pressed"
												"4 green onions, thinly sliced, divided"
												1 1/3 cups grated whole-milk mozzarella cheese (about 6 ounces)
												"4 ounces soft fresh goat cheese, crumbled"
												"8 ounces asparagus, trimmed, each spear cut in half lengthwise, then crosswise into 2- to 3-inch pieces"
												1/2 cup grated Parmesan cheese
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
"Butter 9x13-inch baking dish. Combine 2 1/4 cups water, broth, shallots and marjoram in heavy large Dutch oven; bring to boil. Mix 2 1/2 cups cold water and cornmeal in bowl. Gradually mix cornmeal mixture into broth mixture. Return to boil, stirring constantly. Reduce heat to medium and boil gently until polenta is very thick, stirring often, about 10 minutes. Season with salt and pepper."	"Immediately spread 2 cups polenta in prepared dish. Top with 1 3/4 cups cheese. Drizzle with 1/4 cup cream. Repeat layering, using 2 cups polenta, 1 3/4 cups cheese and 1/4 cup cream. Top with remaining polenta. Spread remaining cheese over. Cover with foil. (Can be made 1 day ahead. Cover and chill. Bring to room temperature before continuing.)"	"Preheat oven to 350°F. Bake covered polenta until hot in center, about 1 hour 15 minutes. Uncover; continue baking until polenta bubbles at edges and top begins to brown, about 10 minutes."									Baked Polenta with Fontina Cheese 	4 3/4 cups water
												2 14 1/2-ounce cans chicken broth
												"5 shallots, minced"
												4 teaspoons dried marjoram
												2 1/2 cups yellow cornmeal
												"1 pound Fontina cheese, grated"
												1/2 cup whipping cream
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
Preheat oven to 350°F.	Pat pork dry and season with salt and pepper. Stir together cornmeal and cumin and transfer to a plate. Turn pork in cornmeal mixture to coat well and discard any remaining mixture.	"Heat oil in a 10-inch nonstick skillet until hot but not smoking and brown pork, turning, about 3 minutes. Transfer pork to a shallow baking pan and roast in middle of oven until a thermometer inserted diagonally at least 2 inches into pork registers 155°F, 30 to 45 minutes. Let stand, loosely covered, 10 minutes. Cut pork into 12 slices (about 1/4 inch thick)."									Cornmeal-and-Chile-Cumin Coated Pork Loin 	"1 1/4 lb boneless pork loin, trimmed"
												2 tablespoons yellow cornmeal
												"1 tablespoon cumin seeds, toasted and coarsely ground"
												1 1/2 teaspoons olive oil
												
												
												
												
												
												
"Put the brisket into a saucepan with the carrots, onions, mustard and the herbs. Cover with cold water, and bring gently to a boil. Simmer, covered, for 2 hours. Discard the outer leaves of the cabbage, cut in quarters and add to the pot. Cook for a further 1 to 2 hours or until the meat and vegetables are soft and tender."	"Serve the corned beef in slices, surrounded by the vegetables and cooking liquid. Serve with lots of floury potatoes and freshly made mustard."										Corned Beef with Cabbage 	4 lb corned brisket of beef
												"3 large carrots, cut into large chunks"
												6 to 8 small onions
												1 teaspoon dry English mustard
												"large sprig fresh thyme and some parsley stalks, tied together"
												1 cabbage
												salt and freshly ground pepper
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
Preheat oven to 400°F with rack in middle. Butter muffin pan if not nonstick.	"Soak raisins in hot water 5 minutes, then drain."	"Meanwhile, whisk together flour, baking powder, baking soda, spices, and salt in a large bowl."	"In a separate bowl, whisk together butter, brown sugar, pumpkin, buttermilk, eggs, and vanilla. Add to dry ingredients and stir until just combined, then stir in raisins and 2 tablespoons pumpkin seeds."	"Divide batter among muffin cups and sprinkle with remaining seeds. Bake until a wooden pick comes out clean, about 20 minutes. Cool slightly on a rack."							Pumpkin Muffins 	1/3 cup golden raisins
												2 cups all-purpose flour
												2 teaspoon baking powder
												1/4 teaspoon baking soda
												1 teaspoon ground cinnamon
												3/4 teaspoon ground ginger
												1/8 teaspoon ground allspice
												1/8 teaspoon ground cloves
												1/2 teaspoon salt
												"1 stick unsalted butter, melted and cooled"
												3/4 cup packed light brown sugar
												3/4 cup canned pure pumpkin
												1/4 cup well-shaken buttermilk
												2 large eggs
												1 teaspoon pure vanilla extract
												"3 tablespoon raw green (hulled) pumpkin seeds (pepitas), divided"
												Equipment: a muffin pan (preferably nonstick) with 12 (1/2-cup) muffin cups
Crack crab shells with kitchen shears and extract meat. Cut enough crab into 1/2-inch pieces to measure 1/2 cup and transfer to a bowl.	Pulse remaining crab in a food processor to finely chop (do not over process).	Add to bowl with remaining ingredients and stir well. Season with salt to taste.	Pack into a 1 1/2 cup crock or bowl and cover surface with plastic wrap.	Chill at least 2 hours. Bring to room temperature before serving.							Potted Crab 	"1 pound frozen Alaskan king crab legs (about 2), thawed"
												"8 tablespoons (1/2 cup) unsalted butter, melted"
												1 1/2 tablespoons medium-dry Sherry
												1/8 teaspoon freshly grated nutmeg
												1/8 teaspoon cayenne
												1 tablespoon finely chopped chives
												1/2 to 1 teaspoon lemon juice (to taste)
												toasted baguette slices
												
Spoon crème fraîche into small bowl; scrape in seeds from vanilla bean and stir to blend. Can be made 1 day ahead. Cover and refrigerate.	*Available at some supermarkets and specialty foods stores.										Vanilla Crème Fraîche 	1 8-ounce container crème fraîche*
												"1/2 vanilla bean, split lengthwise"
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
Peel the asparagus stalks thinly with a vegetable peeler and cut off the tips leaving about 1 1/2-inch (4-cm) stalk attached to them. Cook in boiling salted water for 2 to 3 minutes; the asparagus should be firm but not crunchy. Refresh in cold water and keep at room temperature.	"Melt the butter in a heavy pan, add the beaten eggs, and scramble (click here for instuctions). Add the cream at the end of cooking and season with salt and pepper."	"Steam the crabmeat or shelled claws for 2 to 3 minutes to heat them, then add the asparagus and steam for another minute, until just hot."	"Divide the scrambled eggs between 4 plates. Place 2 crab claws or a pile of crabmeat in the center, arrange the asparagus tips around the crab, scatter with the chives, and serve at once."								Scrambled Eggs with Crab and Asparagus Tips 	36 small asparagus spears
												salt and freshly ground pepper
												6 1/2 tbsp (80g) butter
												"8 eggs, beaten"
												2 tbsp light or heavy cream
												"8 cooked shelled crab claws, or 5 1/2 oz (160g) cooked white crab meat"
												"1 tsp (5g) chives, cut into short lengths"
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
Whisk first 5 ingredients in small bowl to blend; gradually whisk in oil. Season dressing generously with salt and pepper. Toss salad mix in large bowl with 1/4 cup dressing. Divide salad among 4 plates. Tuck mango and avocado into salad; drizzle some of remaining dressing over mango and avocado.											Avocado and Mango Salad with Passion Fruit Vinaigrette 	"3 tablespoons frozen passion fruit juice concentrate, thawed"
												3 tablespoons minced shallot
												4 teaspoons Sherry wine vinegar
												1 teaspoon Dijon mustard
												"1 teaspoon whole coriander seeds, coarsely cracked"
												3 tablespoons olive oil
												8 cups herb salad mix (about 4 ounces)
												"1 large ripe mango, halved, pitted, peeled, sliced"
												"2 small avocados, halved, pitted, peeled, sliced"
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
"In a small bowl whisk together the mustard, the garlic paste, the chopped rosemary, the chopped thyme, the soy sauce, the wine, and salt and pepper to taste, add 2 tablespoons of the oil in a stream, whisking, and whisk the mixture until it is combined well. Brush the lamb generously on all sides with some of the mustard mixture, reserving the remaining mustard mixture, and let it marinate in a lightly oiled roasting pan, covered and chilled, for at least 6 hours or overnight."	"Let the lamb come to room temperature and brush it with the reserved mustard mixture. In a bowl toss the onions with 1 tablespoon of the remaining oil, add the onions and the carrots to the pan, and roast them with the lamb in the middle of a preheated 450°F. oven for 15 minutes. In the bowl toss the potatoes with the remaining 1 tablespoon oil and add them to the pan. Reduce the heat to 350°F. and roast the lamb and vegetables, stirring the vegetables occasionally, for 1 hour and 15 minutes, or until a meat thermometer registers 140°F. for medium-rare meat. Transfer the lamb to a large platter and let it stand for 20 minutes. Transfer the onions and the potatoes with a slotted spoon to a serving dish, leaving the carrots in the pan, and keep them warm, covered."	"Remove the string from the lamb, spoon some of the potatoes and onions around the lamb, and garnish the lamb with the thyme and rosemary sprigs. Serve the lamb, carved, with the gravy."	"Pour off the fat from the pan, add the wine, and deglaze the pan over moderately high heat, scraping up the brown bits. Boil the mixture until it is reduced by half and strain it through a sieve into a saucepan, pressing hard on the carrots. Add the broth and bring the mixture to a boil. In a small bowl knead together the butter and the flour until the mixture is combined well and add the mixture to the gravy a little at a time, whisking. Add any juices that have accumulated on the platter and salt and pepper to taste and simmer the gravy, whisking occasionally, for 3 minutes, or until it is thickened."								Herbed Roast Leg of Lamb with Roasted Onions and Potatoes 	1/3 cup Dijon-style mustard
												"1 large garlic clove, minced and mashed to a paste with 1/4 teaspoon salt"
												1 tablespoon finely chopped fresh rosemary leaves or 1 teaspoon crumbled dried plus fresh rosemary sprigs for garnish
												1 tablespoon finely chopped fresh thyme leaves or 1 teaspoon crumbled dried plus fresh thyme sprigs for garnish
												1 1/2 tablespoons soy sauce
												1/4 cup dry white wine
												4 tablespoons olive oil
												"an 8-pound leg of lamb, the pelvic bone removed and the lamb tied"
												"2 pounds (about 40) small white onions, blanched in boiling water for 2 minutes, drained, and peeled"
												"2 large carrots, cut into 1/2-inch pieces"
												"2 1/2 pounds (about 40) small red or white potatoes, cooked in boiling salted water for 10 minutes, drained, and halved"
												1 cup dry red wine
												2 cups beef broth
												"2 tablespoons unsalted butter, softened"
												3 tablespoons all-purpose flour
"Very thinly slice cucumbers crosswise with slicer; toss with 1 teaspoon salt and drain in a colander 15 minutes. Rinse cucumbers under cold water, then squeeze handfuls to remove excess water; pat dry."	"Stir together wasabi powder and water in a bowl and let stand 5 minutes. Add vinegar, sugar, and soy sauce, whisking until sugar has dissolved. Add cucumbers and toss well."										Cucumbers with Wasabi and Rice Vinegar 	1 pound Japanese or Kirby cucumbers (about 5)
												1/2 teaspoon wasabi powder
												1/2 teaspoon water
												2 tablespoons rice vinegar (not seasoned)
												1 tablespoon sugar
												1/4 teaspoon soy sauce
												an adjustable-blade slicer
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
												
"Blend first 7 ingredients in processor to form paste. Place chicken in 8-inch square baking dish. Spread marinade over, turning to coat. Cover; refrigerate 2 to 4 hours."	"Heat oil in large nonstick skillet over medium-high heat. Sprinkle chicken with salt. Add chicken to skillet; cook until brown, about 2 minutes per side. Add 1/2 cup tangerine juice to skillet. Cover; reduce heat to medium and simmer until chicken is cooked through, turning once, about 5 minutes. Transfer chicken to plates. Add remaining 1/2 cup juice to skillet; boil until thickened, about 2 minutes. Season to taste with salt and pepper. Spoon sauce over chicken. Sprinkle with cilantro."	*Achiote paste is available at Latin markets.									Achiote Chicken with Tangerine Sauce 	2 tablespoons achiote paste*
												1 tablespoon honey
												1 tablespoon red wine vinegar
												1 tablespoon grated tangerine peel (or orange peel)
												2 garlic cloves
												1 teaspoon cumin seeds
												1/2 teaspoon ground cinnamon
												4 skinless boneless chicken breast halves
												1 tablespoon olive oil
												"1 cup fresh tangerine or orange juice, divided"
												Chopped fresh cilantro
"Cook pasta in large pot of boiling salted water until just tender but still firm to bite, about 2 minutes for fresh and 10 minutes for dried. Drain pasta. Return to same pot and toss with oil."	"Combine sauce and wine in heavy medium saucepan. Bring to simmer over medium heat. Mix in tuna and olives, being careful to keep tuna in fairly large pieces. Season with salt and pepper."	"Divide pasta between 2 plates. Using large spoon, make indentation in centers of pasta to create ""nests."" Spoon sauce into centers. Sprinkle each with basil."									Pasta Tonnato Nests 	8 to 9 ounces fresh or dried herb flavored fettuccine
												1 1/2 tablespoons olive oil
												1 cup purchased chunky garden style pasta sauce
												1/4 cup dry red wine
												"1 6-ounce can solid white tuna packed in water, drained"
												1/4 cup sliced pitted brine-cured olives (such as Kalamata)
												2 tablespoons chopped fresh basil
												
											Old-Fashioned 	1 lump sugar
												Dash Angostura bitters
												1 or 2 drops cold water
												2 or 3 ounces bourbon (or any whiskey)
												Twist lemon peel
												Slice orange (optional)
												Maraschino cherry (optional)
												
												
"Prepare barbecue (medium heat). Whisk beer, mustard, oil and thyme in small bowl to blend. Brush both sides of onion slices with some of mustard dressing, being careful to keep slices intact."	"Grill onion and bratwurst until onion is tender and slightly charred at edges and bratwurst is golden brown, turning twice, about 10 minutes for onion and 6 minutes for bratwurst. Grill bread until lightly toasted, about 1 minute per side."	Place toasted bread on plates. Brush with some of mustard dressing. Top bread with bratwurst; separate onion slices into rings and arrange over bratwurst. Drizzle remaining mustard dressing over onions and serve.									Grilled Bratwurst and Onion Open-Face Sandwiches 	1/4 cup beer
												3 tablespoons coarse-grained Dijon mustard
												1 tablespoon vegetable oil
												1 tablespoon chopped fresh thyme or 1 teaspoon dried
												3 1/2-inch-thick red onion slices
												"4 links fully cooked bratwurst (about 10 ounces), halved lengthwise"
												2 slices caraway rye bread (each about 3x5 inches)
												
												
												
												
1. Cook the noodles in plenty of rapidly boiling water until al dente.	"2. Meanwhile, heat the oil in a large skillet or stir-fry pan. Add the onion and sauté over medium heat until golden."	"3. Add all the mushrooms and the wine to the pan. Cover and simmer over low heat until the mushrooms are tender, about 10 minutes. Stir in the tofu and lemon juice and heat gently just until heated through, then remove from the heat. Season to taste with pepper."	"4. Drain the noodles and transfer to a serving dish. Stir in the margarine and season with salt, if desired."	"5. To serve, place a bed of noodles on each plate, then top with some of the mushroom mixture. Garnish each serving with a sprinkling of parsley, if desired, plus a dusting of paprika."							Mixed Mushrooms Stroganoff 	10 to 12 ounces ribbon-style noodles (see Note)
												1 1/2 tablespoons light olive oil
												"1 large onion, chopped"
												"12 to 16 ounces white mushrooms, sliced (see Tip)"
												"4 to 6 ounces fresh shiitake mushrooms, sliced"
												"4 to 6 ounces cremini or baby bella mushrooms, sliced"
												"1/2 cup dry white wine, vegetable stock, or water"
												"One 12.3-ounce container silken tofu, puréed"
												1 tablespoon freshly squeezed lemon juice
												Freshly ground pepper
												2 tablespoons nonhydrogenated margarine
												"Salt, to taste, optional"
												"Minced fresh parsley for topping, optional"
												"Paprika for topping, optional"
												"Use spinach noodles, whole-grain ribbons made of quinoa or spelt flour, or pappardelle, broken into halves or thirds."
"In a saucepan combine the wine, the sugar, the lemon juice, and 1/2 cup water, bring the mixture to a boil, stirring until the sugar is dissolved, and add 2 of the peaches, peeled, halved, and pitted, cut sides down. Simmer the peaches for 10 to 15 minutes, or until they are very tender, and transfer them with a slotted spoon to a blender. Add 1 cup of the cooking liquid and blend the mixture until it is smooth. In a small saucepan sprinkle the gelatin over 1/3 cup cold water, let it soften for 5 minutes, and heat the mixture over low heat, stirring, until the gelatin is dissolved. With the motor running add the gelatin mixture in a stream to the peach mixture until it is combined well. (There will be about 2-1/2 cups peach purée.)"	"Line a 5- to 6-cup terrine or loaf pan with plastic wrap and pour into it about 1/4 cup of the peach purée, or enough to just cover the bottom. Arrange half the strawberries, cut sides down, in one layer on the peach purée and pour enough of the peach purée over the strawberry layer to just cover it. Peel, halve, and pit the remaining 2 peaches, slice them thin, and in a bowl toss them with 1/4 cup of the peach purée. Arrange half the peach slices, overlapping them slightly, over the strawberry layer and pour enough of the remaining peach purée over the peach layer to just cover it."	"In a small bowl toss the raspberries and the blueberries with 1/4 cup of the peach purée and arrange the berries in one layer over the peaches. Pour enough of the remaining peach purée into the terrine to just cover the berries, in the bowl toss the grapes with about 2 tablespoons of the remaining purée, and arrange them in one layer over the berries. Pour enough of the remaining pur��e into the terrine to just cover the grape layer, arrange the remaining peaches in one layer, overlapping them slightly, over the grapes, and pour enough of the remaining purée over the peaches to just cover them. Arrange the remaining strawberries, cut sides up, in one layer over the peaches and cover them with remaining purée. Chill the terrine for 1 hour, or until it is just set, cover it with plastic wrap, and chill it overnight."	"Remove the plastic wrap from the top of the terrine, invert the terrine onto a serving plate, and peel off the plastic wrap carefully. Cut the terrine into 3/4-inch slices with a serrated knife and serve it with the sauce and the mint sprigs."	"In a saucepan combine the sugar, the lemon juice, and 1/4 cup water and bring the mixture to a boil, stirring until the sugar is dissolved. In a blender purée the peaches, peeled, pitted, and chopped, and raspberries with the sugar syrup until the mixture is smooth and force the mixture through a fine sieve set over a bowl, discarding the solids. Chill the sauce, covered, for a least 1 hour or overnight. Makes 2-1/4 cups."							Summer Fruit Terrine 	1 cup dry white wine
												1/2 cup sugar
												3 tablespoons fresh lemon juice
												4 large peaches (about 2 pounds)
												2 envelopes (about 2 tablespoons) unflavored gelatin
												"16 to 18 small strawberries, hulled and halved lengthwise"
												1/2 cup raspberries
												1/2 cup blueberries
												"1/2 cup seedless green grapes, halved lengthwise"
												2 1/4 cups raspberry peach sauce
												1/4 cup sugar
												3 tablespoons fresh lemon juice
												2 large peaches (about 1 pound)
												1-1/2 cups raspberries
												mint sprigs for garnish if desired
